<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>iisacc</title>
    <link>https://iisacc.com</link>
    <description>RSS Feed</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:39:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can Trump realize MAGA</title>
        <link>https://iisacc.com/Posts/Can%20Trump%20realize%20MAGA</link>
        <description>It is undeniable that Donald Trump intuitively pinpointed the critical structural flaws of the American industrial system. The collapse of the manufacturing base, the disconnection between the financial sector and the real economy, the decline of the middle class, the strategic vulnerability of global supply chains, and the resulting weakening of America’s national competitiveness—all of these issues had accumulated long before his presidency. However, it was Trump who, by explicitly raising them as political agendas, brought them to the forefront of public discourse. This is no minor achievement and can be regarded as a pivotal turning point in modern American history.</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://iisacc.com/Posts/Can%20Trump%20realize%20MAGA</guid>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Illusion of Professional Activity</title>
        <link>https://iisacc.com/Posts/The%20Illusion%20of%20Professional%20Activity</link>
        <description>Let us suppose there is a person who has cultivated a refined habit of reading op-eds from prestigious media outlets. This person, once exposed to platforms like YouTube or Netflix—which can dull human intelligence—experiences a disquieting sensation and resolves to assert cognitive control over what they see and hear, striving instead to exercise superior forms of cognition and intellectual ambition. Consequently, the person deliberately devotes several minutes to hours each day to reading specialized books or academic journals in their field on a regular basis.</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://iisacc.com/Posts/The%20Illusion%20of%20Professional%20Activity</guid>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The paradox of technological progress</title>
        <link>https://iisacc.com/Posts/The%20paradox%20of%20technological%20progress</link>
        <description>Humanity has, over the years, advanced not the tangible, but the intangible — digital realms, political ideologies, finance, and services — while neglecting the progress of real, material economies such as medicine, manufacturing, and urban development. JavaScript evolves by the day, yet we still ride automobiles invented over two centuries ago, deluding ourselves into believing civilization has progressed. In truth, these changes hold little real substance in this world. Nothing fundamental has truly changed.</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://iisacc.com/Posts/The%20paradox%20of%20technological%20progress</guid>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>